前情提要
previously on "the 100"...
你要让她的心脏停止跳动吗
you're stopping her heart?
死亡使约瑟芬的思维回到驱动上  我取出驱动之后
death causes her mind to back up onto the drive. i take it out...
再重新启动克拉克的心脏
we get clarke back.
我要重启她的心脏
i need to restart her heart.
她为什么还不醒
why isn't she waking up?
因为约瑟芬还在里面
'cause josephine's still inside.
她死了
she's gone.
不  她没有
no, she's not!
克拉克
clarke?
没人会发现我是个夜血
no one's gonna find out i'm a nightblood.
安静
quiet.
米兰达死了
miranda's dead.
他们会处决你们中的一人
they're executing one of your people tonight.
- 玛蒂  - 不是  她是宿主
- madi?  -  no. she's a host.
除了那孩子  你们剩下的人
the child is spared, but the rest of you
将因自己的罪行 被烧死在火刑柱上
will burn at the stake for your crimes.
把我带到一个能看到行刑的地方
get me to a window with a view of the execution.
瞄准了
got him.
抱歉
sorry.
听说我  你还是能救你妻子的
so listen to me, ok? you can still save your wife.
我们还能制造夜血的
we can still make nightblood.
骨髓
bone marrow.
把他们放下来
take them down.
杰克逊医生
dr. jackson?
我在  玛蒂
i'm here, madi.
我感觉不到我的手了  有点不对劲
i can't feel my hand. something's wrong.
求你帮帮我  我感觉不到了
please help. i can't feel it.
我没法呼吸
i can't breathe.
玛蒂  没事的
madi, it's ok.
艾比  瑞文  埃默里
abby! raven! emori!
你为什么不让我掐他的喉咙
why didn't you let me go for the throat,
我们之前说好的
like we talked about?
我还以为你想要复仇
i thought you wanted revenge.
到你了
your move.
杰克逊是无辜的  他是我们的同伴
because jackson is innocent. he's one of us.
同伴
one of you?
我们说话这会  他在榨干你的骨髓
he's draining your marrow as we speak.
还是来玩游戏吧
let's just play the game.
象棋可不是游戏
chess isn't a game.
这是一堂战略课
a lesson in strategy,
而你却心不在焉
and you're not paying attention.
将军
checkmate.
杰克逊就是个小卒
jackson is a pawn.
要是你之前杀了他  现在我们就自由了
if you had killed him, we'd be free right now
已经在去皇宫的路上了
and on our way to the palace to kill the people
去杀那些谋杀了克拉克的人
who had murdered clarke.
相反  我们现在很可能会像她一样死去
instead we'll now likely die with her,
干得真好
so well done.
你要从我这得到什么
what do you want from me?!
我要你统治这个世界
i want you to rule this world
就像我上次做的一样
as i did the last.
我要你杀掉所有
i want you to kill everyone
挡了你路的人
who gets in your way.
我要你为克拉克报仇
i want you to get revenge for clarke.
告诉我  我要怎么做
tell me what i have to do.
地 球 百 子
第六季        第11集
翻译： 噬魂师
翻译： ASTEROID
翻译： 瑟瑟谷
翻译： 文睿
校对： 噬魂师
时间轴/特效：小螺号
统筹：Kate
总监：麦斯
你没事了
you're ok.
我还在这
i'm still here.
谢谢你
thanks to you.
我睡了多久
how long have i been asleep?
几个小时
a few hours.
对不起  克拉克
i'm so sorry, clarke.
我知道你成了目标
i knew you were a target.
却没保护好你
i didn't protect you.
贝拉米  你救了我
bellamy, you saved me.
我们要怎么去救
so how do we save everyone
那些被我抛下的人
that i left behind?
要是你没这么做  我就死了
you know, if you didn't, i'd be dead.
他们都会这么做的  厄科  玛蒂
they all would-- echo, madi.
约瑟芬会确保他们活下来的
josephine would've made sure of it.
你的计划是好的
your plan was good.
我的计划是用约瑟芬的思维驱动
my plan was to use josephine's mind drive
来做筹码
to bargain for peace,
而现在驱动里已经没有思维了
and now there's no mind on the drive.
我们不需要思维驱动
we don't need the mind drive.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
已经有我了
we've got me.
不  不行
no, no way.
贝拉米  要是我们不把女儿给拉塞尔送回去
bellamy, if we don't give russell his daughter back--
克拉克  一旦他察觉你不是她
clarke, as soon as he realizes you're not her,
你会第二次走进那扇门里
which will be the second you walk in the door
他会检查驱动
and he checks the drive,
你会死的
you're dead.
那我们就把驱动放回去
so let's put it back in.
不可能
that's not happening.
很感激你为我们做的
we appreciate what you did for us,
但这些是我们的人  从现在起我们接手了
but these are our people. we'll take it from here.
这不仅是我们的人的事  贝拉米
this isn't just about our people, bellamy.
都是因为我  克拉克
well, it is for me, clarke.
很好  所有人都醒了
good. everybody's awake.
计划是什么
so what's the plan?
我们就在这浪费时间吧
let's play what's a bigger waste of time, shall we?
想要徒手撬开一把锁
trying to pry off a lock with your bare hands
或是祈祷一个12岁的精神病患者
or praying for a 12-year-old psychopath
来救我们
to come to our rescue.
她不是精神病
she's not a psychopath.
她是一个被恶魔袭击了的孩子
she's a child under assault from a demon.
我们拖的时间越久
and the longer we wait...
她就会被控制得越深
the more control he has over her.
放松
just relax.
瑞文在处理
raven's on the case.
我相信只要霍迪尼·米勒
i'm sure madi will be fine
把我们弄出去  我们得到贝卡的咒语书
as soon as houdini miller breaks us out of here
玛蒂就会没事的
and we get becca's book of spells.
那在机械车间里  对吧
that's from the machine shop, right?
没用
ah! it's no use,
没工具没法打开
not without something to pick it.
哇  真惊讶啊
wow. what a surprise.
你还有更好的主意吗  墨菲
you got a better idea, murphy?
帮我把这搬开
nah. help me get this out of the way.
有人想猜下厄科发生了什么吗
anyone want to take a guess as to what happened to echo?
要是她可以  她一定会救我们的
she would've saved us if she could.
我们得假设  他们现在也抓了她
we have to assume they have her, too, now.
帮他们制造夜血  给我们争取了些时间
making them nightblood bought us some time,
但真有人相信
but does anyone really believe
一旦我们搞定了  他们会就这么让我们走
they're just gonna let us walk once it's done?
把门打开
open it up. let's go.
出来  墨菲
on your feet, murphy.
皇宫里有人要见你
you're wanted in the palac.
你因企图暗杀一名普莱姆
you're guilty of attempting to assassinate a prime
以及散布亵渎神明的谣言而获罪
and spreading blasphemous rumors.
惩罚就是死亡
the punishment for this is death,
但我们能发发善心
but we can be merciful.
你的朋友乔丹救了普莱娅的性命
your friend jordan saved the life of pria vii.
愿她的名为圣
hallowed be her name.
在他的康复过程中  她会亲自照料
she's seen to his ongoing recovery personally.
因为你的罪行是为了拯救你的人民
because your crimes were committed to save your people,
我会仁慈地给你一次机会
i will offer you a chance for mercy as well.
但你得自己去争取
but you have to earn it,
首先告诉我  除了泰
starting by telling us who else you talked to
你还把这事告诉了谁
other than tai.
没人了  就只有他
no one. it was just him.
你没法问他  他告诉了谁  真是太糟了
too bad you can't ask him who he told.
这人杀害了一个普莱姆
the man murdered a prime.
也许你应该对这事
maybe you should take this
更严肃一点
a little more seriously.
那不是杀害
that wasn't murder.
西蒙妮·普莱姆  愿她的名为圣
simone prime, hallowed be her name,
会回来的
will be back.
回不来的生命  那才叫杀害
the life taken to make that happen will be murder.
那个把她带回来的生命
the life taken to make that happen
将会是你的
will be yours.
带她去机械车间
take her to the machine shop.
测试艾比的骨髓公式
test abby's bone marrow formula.
要是有用  把你变成了宿主
if it works and turns you into a host,
成为西蒙妮·普莱姆的一个转世
then it will be your great honor
将会是你莫大的荣誉
to become one with simone prime.
愿她的名为圣
hallowed be her name.
我以前从没做过这种手术
i've never performed that procedure before.
你知道的
you know that.
我也从没要求你这么做过  但我现在要求你
and i never asked you to, but i'm asking you now.
我们受过这方面的训练  所有人都接受过
you're trained for this. we all are.
我们再也没法模糊道德了
and we can no longer afford our moral equivocations,
但这就是我们把家人带回来的方式
but this is how we get our family back.
很好  等准备好了叫我
good. call for me when it's done.
我想在那看着复活
i want to be there for the resurrection.
她跟我走
she comes with me.
我们要去机械车间   把贝卡之书取回来
安静
silence.
在那之前别死了
现在装作你讨厌我
墨菲  你个叛徒  我要杀了你
murphy, you traitor! i'll kill you!
你一直都是个叛徒
you've always been a traitor.
你一直都是个肮脏的
you've always been a filthy--
我要成为谁
so who do i get to be?
你真狡猾  约翰
you're a slippery one, john,
总是做墙头草
always playing both sides of the fence.
我怀疑你从没做过任何
i doubt you've ever done anything
对你没有好处的事
that didn't redound to your own benefit.
拜托  这话可真刻薄
come on. now, that's just mean.
别会错意  我欣赏你这点
don't get me wrong. i like that about you.
是么
oh, you do, huh?
这意味着  只要我的要求对你有好处
it means i can trust you as long as what i'm asking
我就能相信你
has something in it for you.
你的要求是什么
and what are you asking?
根据杰德所言  我女儿还活着
according to jade, my daughter is still alive,
至少昨晚还活着
or was last night.
我要你把她带回来
i need you to bring her home.
要是你做到了  那你和你的女朋友
if you can do this, then you and your girlfriend
就都能得到永生
have your immortality after all.
- 如果我拒绝呢  - 你不会的
- and if i say no? - you won't.
但你如果失败了
if you fail, however,
或是动了手脚  让我的女儿
or do something that keeps my daughter
不能回到我的身边
from her place at my side,
那就不要怪我以眼还眼  以牙还牙了
then i will be forced to take an eye for an eye.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
永生或死亡
immortality or mortality.
听起来很公平
it seems fair.
不是你的眼  约翰
not your eye, john.
埃默里的眼
emori's.
在第二个月亮升起之前完成这件事
you have till second moon.
你是夜血  你能随时进入屏障中
You are nightblood, you can walk through the shield
然后关闭它  为什么不这么做
at any time and lower it. why haven't you?
因为他不想杀死里面的人
because he doesn't want to kill the people inside.
他想救他们  而他们会誓死保护普莱姆家族
he wants to save them, and they'll die to protect the primes.
那就让他们去死  我不会让我的人民
then they die. i'm not letting our people get executed
因为那些人的愚昧妄想而死
because theirs are delusional.
我不知道密码
i don't have the code.
我试过了  没法关闭屏障
i couldn't lower the shield if i tried.
那找赖克呢
what about ryker?
是他建造了这里  还帮你逃走
he built it, and he helped you escape.
去找他  关闭屏障
go to him, you lower the shield,
其余的事  我们来做
we do the rest.
赖克不会帮我们的
ryker won't help us.
他打开了我的牢门
he left my cell door open
是为了阻止西蒙妮把我绑在火刑柱上烧死
to stop simone from burning me at the stake,
但他不会帮我阻止复活
but he wouldn't help me stop the resurrections.
他们想烧死你
they were gonna burn you?
就像烧死魔鬼一样
that's what you do to demons.
我毁掉了胚胎
i destroyed the embryos.
我们带着一千人登陆
we landed with a thousand.
他们经过了基因改造  可以抵抗太阳辐射
genetically engineered with what you call nightblood
你们称之为夜之血脉
to protect against solar radiation.
所以宿主才如此稀少
that's why hosts are so rare--
所以约瑟芬才开始了献祭
why josephine started oblation.
我没想到她会做到这步 但是
i didn't think she would take it that far, but--
所以你的非暴力革命让情况愈演愈烈
so your nonviolent revolution made things worse.
贝拉米  他不想杀死自己的人民
bellamy, he doesn't want to kill his own people.
- 为什么不  你杀过了  - 贝拉米
- why not? you did. - bellamy.
我不需要食人族女王
i don't need a lecture
教我什么是仁义道德
on moral relativity from the queen of cannibals.
我能和你到外面去说话吗
can i talk to you outside?
不  不行  知道么  仅这一次
no. no. you know what? for once, o.,
你不是我最大的麻烦
you're not my biggest problem.
拜托了
please?
去吧  我们继续想办法
go. we'll keep thinking.
你妹妹真是特别
your sister's special.
这样形容她也行
well, that's one word for it.
我是认真的  贝拉米
i'm serious, bellamy.
她进入异象之中  却回来了
she went into the anomaly and came back.
没人做到过这事
no one's ever done that before.
异象
the anomaly?
你听到的那个声音
that sound you hear,
圣所之谜
the great mystery of sanctum.
听着  她什么都不记得了
look, she didn't remember anything,
所以我给了她赤日毒素
so i gave her red sun toxin to help her see.
而她选择了去窥探自己的内心
she chose to look inward instead.
但现在没有日食
but there was no eclipse.
毒素无处不在
the toxin's everywhere--
每一片叶子  每一棵树  大地
in every leaf, in every tree, the soil,
石块
the rocks.
我们逐渐找到了其他方法驾驭这种力量
over time, we found other ways to harness its power.
你们把它武器化了  对吗
you weaponized it, didn't you?
西蒙妮把它武器化了
simone did
作为她调整协议的一部分
as part of her adjustment protocol.
我的研究主要是为了找到解药
my research was focused on an antitoxin.
发现静脉注射之后会导致幻觉
the discovery that intravenous use produced
只是一个意外
a waking dream was a happy accident.
加百列  你的朋友到了
gabriel, your friends are here.
别开枪  我们是一伙的
don't shoot. we're on the same side.
贝拉米  放下枪
bellamy, gun down.
一伙的
same side, huh?
在山洞里的时候  他可是和约瑟芬一起的
he was with josephine in the cave.
- 嘿  嘿  - 是她  约瑟芬·普莱姆
- hey, hey. - it's her--josephine prime.
- 不  不 不 - 举起你的武器
- no, no, no.  - raise your weapons.
- 拿下她  - 她不是
- take her down! - it's not her.
加百列  帮下忙
gabriel,you can do a little help.
泽维尔
xavier?
泽维尔  哥哥  让开
xavier, brother, get out of the way.
蕾拉  没事的
layla, it's ok.
尼尔森  放下武器
nelson, put the weapon down.
所有人  放下武器
all of you, weapons down.
这是命令
that's an order.
你无权发号施令
you don't give orders.
老人在哪里
where's the old man?
蕾拉  检查帐篷
layla, search the tent.
老人死了
the old man is dead.
所以泽维尔也死了
so is xavier.
跪下
on your knees.
加百列
gabriel.
叛徒
traitor!
回去  回去
get back! come on.
蕾拉  冷静
layla, easy!
冷静
easy.
解释一下
explain.
我也不愿意事情变成这样
i didn't want this.
我对泽维尔爱如亲子  你知道的
i loved xavier like a son. you know that.
不许你说他的名字
don't say his name.
蕾拉  如果你不能接受  可以到外面等一下
layla, if you can't handle this, maybe you should wait outside.
我没事  让我听
i'm fine. i need to hear this.
未经我的同意  爱德华多把我带了回来
eduardo brought me back without my consent.
爱德华多已经死了十年了
eduardo's been dead for 10 years,
老人失踪的时候  他被圣所的守卫杀死了
killed by sanctum guards around the time the old man disappeared.
不是圣所的守卫
it wasn't the sanctum guards.
十年
ten years?
他十年来一直在对我们撒谎
he's been lying to us for 10 years,
让我喊他哥哥
letting me call him brother?
他依旧是我们的首领
he's still our leader.
不
no.
他是一个叛徒  普莱姆家族的人
he's a traitor and a prime.
他不可能对我们说实话
he could've told us the truth,
故意让我们认为自己被抛弃了
but instead, he let us think we were abandoned.
把枪给我
now, give me back the gun
让我彻底结束这一切
and let me end this once and for all.
等等
wait.
如果这就是你真正想要的
if this is what you really want,
至少等炸弹做完之后再杀了他
at least wait until he delivers the bomb.
你在说什么
what are you talking about?
闭嘴
shut up.
武器化赤日毒素
i'm talking about weaponized red sun toxin.
加百列是夜之血脉
gabriel's a nightblood.
他可以进入屏障  引爆那些炸弹
he can walk it right through the shield and deploy it.
毒素释放之后  他找到我们的朋友瑞文
once it's in the air, he finds our friend raven.
她会为我们关闭屏障
she'll bring the shield down for the rest of us.
然后趁人群疏散  在一片混乱之中
we use the chaos of the evacuation
营救我们的人
to rescue our people.
你们杀死普莱姆
you kill the primes.
一切结束
that's how this ends.
不错的计划
it's a good plan.
什么  你就这样相信他们了
come on. you trust them just like that?
不  除非
no. but i will...
他杀死约瑟芬·普莱姆
when he kills josephine prime.
我不是约瑟芬
i'm not josephine.
是真的  约瑟芬已经不在了
it's true. josephine's gone.
我亲自取出了她的思维驱动
i took the mind drive out myself.
他在保护她
he's protecting her.
我们还需要更多证据来证明他是个叛徒吗
how much more proof that he's a traitor do we need?
不用了
no.
如果你杀了她  我不会为你制造那些炸弹
if you kill her yourself, i won't build you the bomb.
很好
good.
首先  我们收集毒素
first, we gather the toxin.
在去异象的路上  有一个山洞
there's a cave on the way to the anomaly.
你哪也不准去
you're not going anywhere.
你这位久违的朋友也是
neither is your long-lost friend.
我们可以去
we can do it.
告诉我们要找什么
just tell us what to look for.
可以放开她了
you can let her go now.
所以  就这样吗
so that's it, then?
一针下去  她就是一个宿主了
one shot, and she's a host?
是的
yes.
根据他们医生的说法  还需要一段时间
according to their doctor, we have some time.
我去房间休息了
i'll be in my room.
真相的传播也是如此的简单
the truth spreads like that, too.
当然了  不止一个人知道真相
of course, more than one person knows the truth.
不是吗
don't they?
你们到外面等吧
you guys can wait outside.
不必听她满口谎言
no need to listen to her lies.
你觉得拉塞尔什么时候会发现
how long before russell finds out
你才是那个引发革命的人
you were the one who sparked the revolution?
一个死去的门卫不是革命
one dead janitor isn't a revolution.
我们至少告诉了十几个人
we told at least a dozen others,
但你让他相信  只有泰知道
but you let him believe it was just tai.
你依旧在挣扎
that tells me you're still torn.
你说的没错  是的
you're right. i am.
我的人被活活烧死至少比
the only thing worse than my people being burned alive
我的家人被烧死好
is it happening to my family.
赖克  等等  真相已经大白
ryker, wait. the truth is out.
想要阻止已经太晚了
it's too late to stop this.
如果你放我走  我还是会遵守我们的约定
if you let me go, i'll still honor our deal.
你和你的母亲不会有事
you and your mother will be fine.
不  不可能
no, we won't.
我们是否做了正确的事已经不重要了
it won't matter that we do the right thing.
人们会需要鲜血
the people will need blood.
守卫会誓死保卫我们
the guards will die defending us.
告诉我
tell me something.
如果你杀一人
if you could prevent all those deaths
能救百人   你会选择怎么做
by taking one life, would you do it?
我就是这么想的
that's what i thought.
对不起  厄科  我真的很抱歉
i'm sorry, echo. i truly am.
该死
damn it!
他们到底在哪里
where the hell are they?
指挥官驱逐你的时候
you didn't follow orders
你没有服从命令
when the commander banished you.
为什么
how come?
有时我们必须违抗
sometimes we have to disobey
才能超越
in order to transcend.
在我们跟踪那个金发女郎的时候
did you think about that
你也是这么想的么
when we were following blodreina?
失误是可以原谅的
mistakes are forgivable.
但不能重蹈覆辙
not learning from them isn't.
吃饭时间  你们知道规矩
meal time. you know the drill.
把手放在墙上
hands on the wall.
你在干什么
what are you doing?
我说  把手放在墙上
i said, hands on the wall.
超越
transcending.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
让他们挨饿吧
let 'em starve.
你在想什么
what were you thinking?
这是自方舟以来
that's the best lift i've made...
我做过的最好的一次
since the ark.
很好  把刀藏起来  我会让他们回来的
impressive. hide the blade. i'll get them to come back.
等等  等等  等等  等等
wait. wait. wait. wait.
我偷到的可不只那把刀
i didn't steal it for the blade.
机械车间在这边  来吧
machine shop's this way. come on.
这些设备是我离开的原因之一
a device like this was one of the reasons i left.
我不会给拉塞尔制造炸弹的
i wouldn't build russell his bomb,
但我会给你做一个
and here i am building one for you.
别管我
never mind me.
我在自言自语
i'm rambling.
你的朋友们应该已经在山洞里了
your friends should be at the cave by now.
你知道  不幸的是他们已经服用了抗毒血清
you know, it's too bad they took an antitoxin.
兄妹的关系
that is one sibling relationship that could use
其实可以用幻觉好好引导
a good guided hallucination.
是啊  如果在他们发现之前
yeah. be a shame if one of them was murdered
其中一个就被杀了  那就太可惜了
before they worked it out.
蕾拉  我
layla, i'm--
你还敢道歉
don't you dare apologize.
这个炸弹  如果普莱姆家族有一个
this bomb. if the primes have one,
那他们为什么不用在我们身上呢
then why haven't they used it on us?
我不知道
i don't know.
可能是把我们变成狂暴的杀手
probably because turning us into raging killers
不符合他们的利益
isn't in their best interest.
那是为什么
then what's it for?
约瑟芬和西蒙妮对那些
josephine and simone were intrigued
在日蚀的幻觉中存活下来的人
by a pattern in the visions of those who survived
很感兴趣
being caught out in the eclipse.
尽管我尽力阻止他们
despite my best efforts to stop them,
他们为了研究
they started leaving test subjects outside
开始把受试者留在外面
to study it.
现在  毫不惊讶
now, not surprisingly, believers
信奉普莱姆家族是神的信徒们
in the divinity of the primes
总是宣称我们是堕神
invariably reported seeing us as gods
或是堕天使
or as angels.
更让莱特伯恩们感兴趣的是
what interested the lightbournes more
忠实信徒总是喜欢攻击
was that the aggression response of the faithful
那些不那么虔诚的人
was almost always aimed at the less devout.
信徒杀害非信徒
believers killing nonbelievers.
没错
我以我兄弟的记忆起誓
i swear on my brother's memory,
如果你背叛我们  我会杀了你
if you betray us, i will kill you.
约瑟芬是对的
josephine was right.
气象山上的一切又重演了
this is mount weather all over again.
那颗炸弹带来的不只是混乱
that bomb won't just cause chaos.
而是大屠杀
it'll cause a massacre.
一定有比利用屠杀
there has to be a better way
分散注意力来关掉护盾
than using a massacre as a distraction
更好的方法
to get the shield down.
听着  如果你担心你的人民  他们不会有事的
look, if you're worried about your people, they'll be fine.
一旦触发预警系统并开始疏散
put in wall restraints to fend for themselves
他们就会启用墙上的约束装置
as soon as the early warning system
来保护自己
is triggered and evacuation begins.
我告诉你  我不只是担心
i told you, i'm not just worried about--
预警系统
the early warning system.
昆虫会首先受到毒素的影响
the insects are affected by the toxin first.
这就是为什么他们会躲在圣所的龟壳里
that's why they're in tanks all over sanctum.
我知道  我也为这事头痛  所以你想说什么
i'm aware. it was my idea. what's your point?
我们使用较少量的毒素
we use less of the toxin--
足够影响昆虫而不影响人类
enough to affect the bugs but not the people.
这就足以触发警报
just enough to trigger the evacuation.
你能做到么
can you do that?
可以  但是如果没有引起骚动
yes. but without the chaos,
我就没有足够的时间去关掉护盾
i won't have time to take the shield down.
你的人也还是囚犯
your people will still be prisoners,
普莱姆家族还是普莱姆家族
and the primes will still be primes.
不过我们会杀死很多虫子
we will kill some bugs, though.
所以我们先关闭护盾
so we take down the shield first.
先关闭护盾  在疏散之前
first, as in before the evacuation,
每个人都在家的时候
while everyone's still at home?
听着  克拉克  恕我直言
look, clarke, i don't mean to be rude, but--
约瑟芬可以做到
josephine could do it.
你觉得你能让你的子嗣们
think you can get your children
同意你和我一起去么
to let me go with you?
不确定  他们不会想这样的
it's doubtful. they're not gonna like it.
贝拉米也是
neither is bellamy.
我们都知道  加百列
we got this, gabriel.
小心点
careful.
加百列说
gabriel said these things have
这些东西里的赤日毒素含量
the highest concentration of red sun toxin
是他们已知的最高含量
they've ever found.
相信我  他们可比
trust me, they're a hell of a lot stronger
毒坚果厉害得多
than jobi nuts.
那么  跟我说说异象吧
so tell me about this anomaly.
加百列说你进去了  又出来了
gabriel says that you went in and you came back,
你很特殊
you were special.
我不特殊
i'm not special.
我在迪约扎之后进去
i went in after diyoza,
但我没赶上她
but i couldn't catch her.
迪约扎死了么
diyoza's dead?
是  光吞没了她
yeah. the light swallowed her,
但把我吐了出来
but it spit me out.
我不知道为什么
i didn't know why.
现在我知道了
but now i do.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
是因为你
it was for you.
因为我  好吧
for me? right.
当对不起已经不能表达情感的时候  你会怎么办
what do you say when "i'm sorry" isn't good enough?
嘿  继续采
hey. don't stop.
你把我丢下是对的
you were right for leaving me behind.
我知道这对你来说有多难
i know how hard that must have been for you,
但你是对的
but you were right.
我当时一团糟  对你来说很危险
i was a mess-- a danger to you,
对我来说也是
to myself,
还有所有我们在乎的人
and everyone we care about.
是么  呃  现在有什么不一样了
yeah? well, what's changed?
一切
everything.
这么多么
that much, huh?
啊  这些菌类毒素一定很强
ah, the mushrooms must be strong.
我这一生都需要你  贝尔
i need you in my life, bell.
听着  我不知道在你身上发生了什么
look, i don't know what happened to you out here,
但现在不是时候
but now is not the time.
我们要在抗毒血清失效之前
we need to fill these bags and get back to camp
把这些袋子装满然后回到营地
before the antitoxin wears off.
你是我的基石
you were my rock.
如果没有你
without you as my compass,
我就会迷失
i was lost.
我找不到走出黑暗的道路
i couldn't find my way out of the dark.
我做过的事
i did things...
那些无法挽回的事
things i can't take back...
这些事会
things that will haunt me
一直困扰我的一生
until the day i die.
我不是在请求你原谅
i'm not asking you for forgiveness.
我知道  我必须要
i know i have to earn that
赢得你的信任
along with your trust.
你想要我说什么
what do you want me to say, o.?
说我是你的妹妹
say i'm your sister.
你是我的妹妹
you're my sister...
但你不是我的责任
but you're not my responsibility.
不再是了
not anymore.
走吧  采得够多了  我随后就来
go on. we got enough. i'll be right behind you.
看那个
look at that.
生效了
it worked.
等等  你要去哪
wait. where are you going?
去告诉拉塞尔  我们已经解决了宿主的问题
to tell russell we've solved our host problem.
希望他能为你杀了我  哈
hoping he'll kill me for you, huh?
他不会的  你知道的
he won't, you know.
这是个忠诚测试
it's a loyalty test.
相信我  我曾经也这样过
trust me. i've been there.
我知道你在经历什么
i know what you're going through.
你什么都不知道  你是个杀手  是个刺客
you know nothing. you're a killer, an assassin.
而我是工程师
i'm an engineer.
今天以后你就不会这样了
you won't be just that after today.
好吧  如果他想让我亲手来
fine. if he wants me to do it myself,
我就亲手来
i'll do it myself.
实际上  我希望你能放我走
actually, i was hoping you'd let me go.
不可能
it's not gonna happen.
我做出了选择
i've made my choice.
现在  一切都太晚了
it's too late to change that now.
不  不晚
no, it isn't.
至少
at least...
让我告诉你我身上都发生了什么
let me tell you what happened to me--
那些我从未告诉过别人的事情
something i've never told anyone else.
你在拖延时间
you're stalling.
好吧
ok.
告诉我你的故事
tell me your story.
快点
quickly.
要比那更准
top that.
你知道  我做不到的
you know i can't.
你想让她认为你无能么
do you want her to think you're useless?
按我教你的做
do it like i showed you,
想象一下尼亚女王的脸在中间
and picture queen nia's face at the center.
哈哈哈  好
ha ha! ok.
那就是你的秘密吗
is that your secret, then?
陛下  请原谅
your highness, forgive--
闭嘴  我不在乎你瞄准的是什么
quiet. i don't care why your aim is true--
能中就行
just that it is.
是时候了  厄科
it's time, echo.
沙漠人3天后等着
sangedakru is expecting you
你的加入
in 3 days.
你已经掌握了他们的方言
you've mastered their dialect,
学习了他们的习俗
studied their customs,
但你准备好为你的女王杀人了吗
but are you ready to kill for your queen?
准备好了  陛下
yes, highness.
证明给我看
prove it.
这个杂种是个沙漠人间谍
this piece of filth is a sangedakru spy.
如果他逃跑的话  你的任务就失败了
if he gets away, your mission will fail.
艾什  把弓给她
ash, hand her the bow.
跑啊  你个傻子
run, you fool!
你还在等什么呢
what are you waiting for?
想象我的脸在他的后背上
imagine my face on his back.
犹豫就是死亡
hesitation is death.
拉弓放箭
take the shot.
懦弱
weakness!
我不能派一个害怕杀戮的刺客过去
since i can't send an assassin who's afraid to kill,
我再给你最后一次机会
i'll give you one last chance.
杀了她
kill her.
如果她没有在3秒内拿起刀子发起进攻
if she doesn't take the knife and attack in 3 seconds,
把她俩都杀了
kill both.
1...
2...
反抗啊
fight back.
向她证明  她也需要你
show her she needs you, too.
结果她  否则你就死定了
finish her, or you're finished.
我很抱歉
i'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
i'm sorry, too.
沙漠人正在等一个
sangedakru is expecting
叫厄科的女孩儿
a girl named echo.
恭喜你  厄科
congratulations, echo.
不要让我失望
don't let me down.
让她做好准备
get her ready.
我猜你可以说
i guess you could say
我早就被人抹去了
i've been wiped before.
很遗憾听到这些
i'm sorry that happened.
我告诉你这些不是为了
i didn't tell you that
让你不要杀我
just so you don't kill me.
我是想告诉你  如果你杀了我
i told you to spare you from what happens
不要为此感到愧疚
if you do.
我相信你说的没错  艾什
i'm sure you're right...ash.
杀了你会让我备受折磨
killing you would haunt me,
但不杀你同样也会折磨我
but so would not killing you.
我们都知道如果我放你走的话
we both know what would happen to sanctum
圣所会有什么下场
if i let you go.
我很抱歉
i'm sorry.
不  不
no. no.
好吧
fine.
守卫  进来
guards, come in.
把门关上
close the door.
我需要你们帮我按住她
i need your help holding her down.
敢动的话
you move...
你就死定了
you die.
这么晚才来
took you long enough.
我们是来拿笔记本的
we came for the notebook.
我们事先不知道  否则我们就
we didn't know, or we would've--
你是夜之血脉
犹豫就是死亡
hesitation is death.
什么叫你不是在制作炸弹
what you mean you're not building a bomb?
把它释放到水中会让它
releasing it in the water will cause it to aerosolize
以较低的浓度雾化
at a lower concentration.
我们在不引发大规模
we'll trigger an evacuation
精神错乱的情况下启动疏散机制
without inducing a mass psychosis.
换句话说  不要再让无辜的人死去了
in other words, no innocent people die.
他们要多久才能意识到
how long until they realize
根本就没有日食然后回防呢
there's no eclipse and turn around?
时间不是很长
not long enough.
我们得在那之前进去
we'll need to be inside before it starts,
这意味着
which means--
这意味着屏障需要在启动前拆除掉
which means the shield needs to be down before it starts.
你能悄无声息地做到这一点吗
can you do that without a distraction?
能做到就不是他了
it wouldn't be him.
贝拉米  这是唯一的办法
bellamy, it's the only way.
什么办法
what is?
我扮成约瑟芬
i go as josephine.
这不是唯一的办法
it's not the only way.
我们照原计划使用炸弹
we use the bomb as planned.
在非必要的时候  拿你的生命去冒险是
risking your life when we don't have to is just--
是更好的做法
is how we do better.
蒙蒂会怎么做呢
what would monty do?
克拉克  如果你失败了
clarke, if you fail,
如果拉塞尔知道他女儿死了
if russell figures out that his daughter is dead,
我们所有人就都死定了
all our people are dead, too.
所以我是不会失败的
so i won't fail.
贝拉米  如果我们可以
bellamy, if we can spare
拯救无辜的生命  我们应该拯救
innocent lives, we should.
喂  那是什么
hey, what's that?
骑手来了
got raiders coming!
圣所的骑手
sanctum raiders!
在这儿等着
wait here.
大家都分散开
everybody spread out!
带他们回去
get them back inside.
把他们和普莱姆们一起绑起来  堵住他们的嘴
i want them tied up and gagged with the primes.
蕾拉  你和他们一起去  杀掉所有反抗的人
layla, you're with them. kill anyone who resists.
去拦住他们
move to intercept!
以利亚  洛根  到高地上去
elijah, logan, get to high ground!
我需要有人到高处查看情况
i need eyes up top.
剩下的人  都分散开
the rest of you, spread out.
从另一侧拦截他们
cut them off on the other side!
圣所的骑手
sanctum raiders!
撤退
retreat!
你好啊
hey there.
约瑟芬
josephine?
干得漂亮  杰德
well done, jade.
你就那么喜欢当墙头草  是不是  约翰
you just can't pick a side, can you, john?
我这么做只是因为  如果不这样的话
the only reason i'm doing this is because emori dies
埃默里就会死去
if i don't.
厄科也遇到了麻烦
echo's in trouble, too.
我保证我会尽最大努力帮她的
i promise i'll do what i can for her.
给我们两秒钟时间确保已经安全了
give us two seconds to make sure it's clear,
然后再跟上来
then follow.
不
no.
我来杀掉这个
this one's mine.
去吧  确保一切都安全了
go. make sure it's clear.
她这次真的消失了吗
is she really gone this time?
是的
yes. boo-hoo.
只要我现在扣动了扳机
now, as soon as i pull this trigger,
你设立的小圈套就失败了
your little decoy trick will fail.
你最好赶紧跑吧
you better run.
我能做到的
i can do this.
关掉那个屏障
get that shield down.
我会带骑手过来的
i'll bring the cavalry.
为了蒙蒂
for monty.
她不是约瑟芬
she isn't josephine.
没错  她不是
no, she's not.
你能走快点儿吗
you mind walking a little faster?
别紧张  如果他们想杀我们的话  我们早就死了
relax. if they were gonna kill us, we'd be dead by now.
他们知道我们在这里
they know that we're here.
怎么  不抱一下吗
what? no hug?
约瑟芬
josephine.
这怎么可能呢
how is this possible?
说来话长
it's a long story.
我只想说  我太厉害了
suffice to say, i'm awesome.
然而  我现在无法永生了
what i'm not, however, is immortal.
加百列取出了我的驱动
gabriel took out my drive.
我真的不想打断你们  但是
i really do hate to interrupt, but...
我是个守信用的人
i'm a man of my word.
你在这里赢得了一席之地
you earned your place here.
把他带到埃默里那儿
take him to emori,
把医生和她手下的人都赶出实验室
and clear the doctor and the rest of her people from the lab.
妈妈呢
where's mom?
出了一个意外  不过没事的
there was an incident, but it's ok.
我现在正要去拯救她
i was just on my way to resurrect her,
但我们可以等一下
but that can wait.
让谁拯救她
resurrect her in who?
艾比做到了
abby did it.
我们可以创造宿主了
we can make hosts.
是的  但不是像你想得那样  来吧
yes, but not how you think. come on.
好好检查一下你的身体
let's get you checked out.
我利用克拉克的神经网络
so i used clarke's neural mesh
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177
来留在她的大脑里
to stay in her brain.
变成了一项公平竞争  是不是
turnabout's fair play. am i right?
不管怎么说  我在思维空间里杀了她
anyway, i killed her in the mindspace.
结果就是这样
now here we are.
下次我们得选一个不那么拥挤的宿主
how about next time, we choose a less crowded host?
你觉得呢
what do you say?
这又是哪一出啊
and what is this?
这就是我们
this is how we...
制造宿主的方法
make hosts.
骨髓吗
bone marrow?
克拉克  是你吗
clarke, is that you?
不  我不是  尽管她奋力抵抗了  孩子
no. it's not. she put up a good fight, though, kid.
但她没有赢
can't win them all.
我们会杀了你
we're gonna kill you!
我们会杀了你们所有人
we're gonna kill all of you
以及所有你们爱的东西
and everything you love!
在她死之前  我们能从她身上
hmm. how many doses can we get out of her
提取多少骨髓
before she dies?
不过无所谓了
you know what? never mind.
该启动我的新驱动了
it's time for my new drive.
做一个凡人真是糟糕透了
being mortal sucks.